const hollywoodyQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'In golf, the club known as the 1-wood is commonly referred to as the what?.',
        answer: 'The Driver',
        explanation: 'Woods are numbered in ascending order starting with the driver, or 1-wood, which has the lowest loft (usually between 9 and 13 degrees), and continuing with progressively higher lofts and numbers. Most modern woods are sold as individual clubs allowing the player to customize their club set, but matched sets of woods, especially as part of a complete club set, are readily available.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Charles Hardin Holley (September 7, 1936 – February 3, 1959), known professionally as Buddy Holly, was an American musician and singer-songwriter who was a central and pioneering figure of mid-1950s rock and roll. While travelling to a show, he chartered an airplane to travel to his next show, in Moorhead, Minnesota. Soon after takeoff, the plane crashed, killing Holly, Ritchie Valens, The Big Bopper, and pilot Roger Peterson in a tragedy later referred to by Don McLean as "The Day the Music Died". In what state did the plane crash?',
        answer: 'Iowa',
        explanation: "On February 2, before their appearance in Clear Lake, Iowa, Holly chartered a four-seat Beechcraft Bonanza airplane for Jennings, Allsup, and himself, from Dwyer Flying Service in Mason City, Iowa. Holly's idea was to depart following the show at the Surf Ballroom in Clear Lake and fly to their next venue, in Moorhead, Minnesota. The pilot, Roger Peterson, took off in inclement weather, although he was not certified to fly by instruments only. Shortly after 12:55 am on February 3, 1959, Holly, Valens, Richardson, and Peterson were killed instantly when the aircraft crashed into a frozen cornfield five miles northwest of Mason City, Iowa, airport shortly after takeoff. The three musicians, who were ejected from the fuselage upon impact, suffered severe head and chest injuries. Holly was 22 years old."
    },
    {
        question: "The Resolute desk is a nineteenth-century partners' desk used by several presidents of the United States in the White House Oval Office as the Oval Office desk. It was a gift from Queen Victoria to President Rutherford B. Hayes in 1880 and was built from the English oak timbers of the British Arctic exploration ship HMS ________.",
        answer: 'Resolute',
        explanation: 'It was made from the wood of the ship.'
    },
    {
        question: 'The HOLLYWOOD sign in Los Angeles California is constructed of 9 large, white letters in the Hollywood Hills of the Santa Monica mountains. Within 4 feet, how tall are the letters?',
        answer: '45 feet tall',
        explanation: 'The entire sign is 350 feet long. We will accept 41 to 49 feet as an answer.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Woody Harrelson received a BA in theatre and English in 1983 from Hanover College in Hanover, Indiana. During his time there, he cross paths with a future Vice President of the United States. Which Vice President was it?',
        answer: 'Vice President Mike Pence',
        explanation: "'I knew him, yeah. We were both very religious. It was a Presbyterian college at the time, and I was there on a Presbyterian scholarship, and he was involved with the church activities. I was actually considering being a minister and then I just kind of went a different way...I actually quite liked him. I thought he was a pretty good guy. He's, you know, very religious. Very committed. Seeing as how I'm not quite in that ballpark now, I don't know how we'd get along, 'cause I think he's still quite religious and just a whole different brand of religious. That kind of fervor that you really don't want.' -Woody Harrelson"
    },
    {
        question: 'How much wood could a woodchuck chuck... wait... Woodchucks are just groundhogs. What day is Groundhog Day celebrated on every year?',
        answer: 'February 2',
        explanation: 'Groundhog Day is a popular American tradition observed in the United States and Canada on February 2nd. It derives from the Pennsylvania Dutch superstition that if a groundhog emerging from its burrow on this day sees its shadow due to clear weather, it will retreat to its den and winter will persist for six more weeks; but if it does not see its shadow because of cloudiness, spring will arrive early.'
    },
    {
        question: 'In the animated movie series, Toy Story, the character of Woody is voiced by actor Tom Hanks... or also known as the husband of what american actress/singer/songwriter?',
        answer: 'Rita Wilson',
        explanation: 'Wilson married actor Tom Hanks in 1988. They have two sons, Chester and Truman.'
    },
    {
        question: "What color is Woody Woodpecker's head?",
        answer: 'Red',
        explanation: 'Google it. It is red.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Elijah Wood is an american actor best known for playing Frodo in the Lord of the Rings trilogy. In 1989, he also played a lesser known character dubbed Video Game Boy in the second film of what time-travelling-trilogy.',
        answer: 'Back to the Future',
        explanation: 'At Eight Years Old. This gives ‘Back To The Future’ a whole new meaning. Elijah Wood played a small part in the 1989 film, ‘Back To The Future Part II,’ playing “Video Game Boy” in a scene with Michael J. Fox. At eight years old, it was his first big role.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What type of wood tree has the common helicopter seed pods?',
        answer: 'Maple Trees',
        explanation: 'Helicopter seedpods, also called "samaras," are produced by maple trees. The pods vary in size and shape depending on the species of tree, but all maples produce some version of the distinctive seedpod. Samaras, or "maple keys," are dropped in late summer or early fall before the trees have lost their leaves.'
    }
];

module.exports = hollywoodyQuestions;